数十亿年前
Billions of years ago…
一群不朽者掌握了宇宙间最强大的能量
a race of immortals harnessed the most powerful force in existence:
绿色的意志力量
The emerald energy of willpower.
这群不朽的宇宙守卫者
These immortals, the Guardians of the Universe…
建立了一个世界 守望着宇宙间的一切
built a world from where they could watch over all of existence:
欧阿行星
The planet Oa.
他们将宇宙分为3600个扇区
They divided the universe into 3600 sectors.
一枚意志力附魔的戒指被分配到每个扇区来招募成员
A ring powered by the energy of will was sent to every sector to select a recruit.
能被戒指选中
In order to be chosen by the ring,
传说必须是“无畏者”
it was said one must be without fear.
3600名成员一起…
Together, these 3600 recruits…
组成了银河和平保卫者 名曰“绿灯军团”
formed the intergalactic peacekeepers known as the Green Lantern Corps.
《绿灯侠》
军团历尽劫难
Of all the threats the Corps ever faced…
最大的威胁是恐惧化身的实体 名曰“视差怪”
the gravest was an entity of fear known as Parallax.
唯独传奇绿灯侠 阿宾·苏尔…
Only the legendary Green Lantern Abin Sur…
能将这匹恶魔捕获并囚禁
was capable of capturing and imprisoning this beast…
在失落的行星莱厄特 他成功了
which he did on the lost planet of Ryut.
（莱厄特行星： 失落的扇区）
（探索者6号呼叫基地： 我们的飞船坠毁于失落扇区的东北）
（请求立即支援）
你们害怕了
You are afraid.
很好
Good.
- 我是说 总是要讨论这个 - 不是每次都得说
- I mean, we go into this every time. - It's not every time.
不 亲爱的 想想以前的 想一想吧
No, honey. Think back. Think back. Think back.
上一次我是没事 我真的没事 你的工作对我没有问题
I was fine the last time. I'm usually fine. I'm fine with your work.
- 我能和你谈谈吗？ - 你当然可以了
- Can I just tell you something? - Of course you can.
- 我害怕 亲爱的 - 嘘 嘘
- I'm scared, honey. - Shh, shh.
都没事吧？
Is everything okay?
你知道你妈妈总是在试飞的前夜焦虑不安
Oh, you know how Mom gets the night before a test flight.
但你不害怕吧 爸爸？
But you're not scared, are you, Dad?
应该说是我的工作不允许
Let's just say it's my job not to be.
晚安 儿子
Good night, son.
哈尔 你要迟到了
Hal, you're gonna be late.
早 妈妈 得走了
Good morning, Mom. Gotta go.
爸爸！爸爸！
Dad! Dad! Dad!
- 你认为会突破3马赫速度吗？ - 不久我们就会知道
- You think she'll break mach 3? - We'll find out soon enough.
你不是应该在学校吗？
Hey, shouldn't you be in school?
费瑞斯先生调高了机尾的稳定器
Mr. Ferris raised the rear stabilizer.
他是调高了
Yes, he did.
偏航率陀螺仪已校准了 但倾斜角偏低了2度
The yaw rate gyros are calibrated, but the pitch is off 2 degrees.
- 我会适应的 惯性导航系统怎样？ - 准备好了
- I can live with that. How about the INS? - Good to go.
- 好 - 强尼
- Okay. - Johnny.
- 务必检查一下点火顺序 - 没问题
- Be sure to check the ignition sequences. - No problem.
- 查过了 卡尔 两次 - 好的
- We did, Carl, twice. - Right.
还有陀螺仪呢？做过陀螺仪校准吗？
And, uh, the gyros? Did we do the gyro calibrations?
嗨 卡尔
Hey, Carl.
也许哈尔愿意上你的办公室和凯罗尔一起
Maybe Hal would like to join Carol up in your office.
他们两个可以一起观看试飞
The two of them can watch together.
来吧 年轻人 去见凯罗尔吧
Come on, young man. Let's go find Carol.
哈尔
Hal.
替我暖着
Keep it warm for me.
- 嗨 - 哦 哈克特
- Hi. - Oh, hey, Hector.
嗯 我有了这本书
Hey. So, um, I have this book.
是关于外星球存在生命的可能性
It's about the possibility of life on other planets.
- 酷 - 差不多是存在的 但…
- Cool. - Well, it almost has to exist, but…
- 哈尔！ - 凯罗尔
- Hal! - Hey, Carol.
哈克特 你还在卖风火轮吗？
Hector. You still wanna trade Hot Wheels?
是的
Sure.
瞧瞧谁在这里 是我们将来的试飞员
Well, look who's here. Our future test pilot.
夹克很配你 孩子
Jacket suits you, son.
- 嗨 爸爸 - 嗨
- Hi, Dad. - Hey.
我总是和哈克特说 书很有趣 但偶尔…
I keep telling Hector, books are fun, but every once in a while…
飞出这个世界也并不是一个坏主意 对吗 哈尔？
it's not such a bad idea to get out in the world, right, Hal?
- 嗨 鲍伯 - 当前的大人物
- Hey, Bob. - The man of the hour.
没有像第一次试飞这样让我热血沸腾的了 是吧 卡尔？
Nothing like a first flight to get the blood boiling, eh, Carl?
爸爸 我们能在场地上观看试飞吗？
Dad, can we watch from down in the field?
- 可以 - 太棒了！
- Sure. - Yes!
- 你们要小心点 - 和工程师们在一起
- You kids be careful. - Stay with the engineers.
去啊 儿子 看得更近一些
Go on, son. See it up close.
不用了 爸爸 我没事的
That's okay, Dad. I'll be fine.
指挥塔 我是军刀一号 已准备起飞
Ferris Tower, Sabre One, ready for take-off.
请求无限制爬升 飞行水平高度450
Request unrestricted climb, flight level 450.
好！好！
Yes! Yes!
军刀一号 同意你无限制爬升
Sabre One, unrestricted climb approved.
到达1万英尺高度时联系费瑞斯起飞点
On passing 10, 000 feet, contact Ferris Departure.
你已准许起飞了 祝好运 军刀
You're cleared for take-off. Good luck, Sabre.
（今日）
（2814扇区）
辛纳斯丘 我现在是最大速度航行了 告诉凡塔拉我将…
Sinestro, I'm traveling at maximum velocity. Tell Fentara I should…
凡塔拉死了
Fentara is dead.
行星居民呢？
The planet's inhabitants?
你不必撤离他们了
Your mission to evacuate them is no longer necessary.
和塔洛克的情况一样
It's just as it was on Talok.
所有生命体都被毁灭 生命精华被吸干
Every life form destroyed and their essence absorbed.
到处是黄色能量的痕迹
Traces of yellow power everywhere.
守卫者呢？
And the Guardians?
守卫者们销声匿迹了
The Guardians are silent.
我要求一位观察者…
I've demanded an audience with them.
阿宾·苏尔…
Abin Sur.
我身负重伤
I'm badly wounded.
前往最近的可居住行星 开始挑选程序
Heading to the nearest inhabited planet for the selection process.
通知守卫者们 是视差怪
Tell the Guardians it's Parallax.
噢 不！
No. No.
抱歉 要闪了 你就当在自己家
Sorry, I gotta run. Make yourself at home, okay?
那什么 要喝水有自来水
There's, uh, water in the tap.
不！
No!
混蛋
Asshole.
费瑞斯军刀三号 是人工智能战机的艺术典范
The Ferris Sabre III is state-of-the-art of artificial-intelligence fighter planes.
具备人类驾驶员飞行和格斗的一切能力
It has all of the flying and combat capability of a human pilot…
却不似人类那样犯错
but with none of the human error that comes with it.
将军 卡尔可不是为了得到合同而吹牛
Carl isn't just blowing smoke to get a contract, general.
你的幕僚 他的承包商 我的办公室 都参与其中
Your staff, these contractors, my office…
全程我们参与了
we've all been part of this from the ground up.
钦佩备至 参议员
Well, I appreciate that, senator.
今天 要大显身手
But today the rubber meets the road.
在一个模拟战斗环境
We have a simulated combat situation.
两架军刀对阵卡尔的两个王牌
Two Sabres against Carl's two best pilots.
嘿凯罗尔 我今天想飞一下 你觉得如何
Carol. Was gonna do a little flying today. What do you think?
我觉得你迟到了
I think you're late.
没错 只是因为睡过头了
Yes, but that's only because I slept in.
我也曾睡过头 但是在11岁以前
I used to sleep in. Then I turned 11.
我提醒你
Let me give you a little heads-up.
我一整周都在对付这个两架军刀 次次被它们羞辱
I've gone up against these Sabres all week and they smoked me every time.
你能做的一切 它都胜你一筹
There isn't anything you can do that they can't do better, faster…
并且从不让女人失望
and without disappointing women everywhere.
你我都清楚 那是胡扯
I, uh, think we both know that's not true.
这就是为什么我不想你参加 可我父亲坚持
This is exactly why I didn't want you for this. My father did.
我希望是詹森
I would've gone with Jensen.
我也希望是詹森 不巧 他忙 而且也不咋的
I'd have too, but unfortunately he's busy not being good enough.
起码他不迟到
At least he shows up.
哈尔
Hal…
今天的测试 很重要
this test today, it's important.
我了解 你上天后有好瞧的 别着急 好吗
I'm gonna make you look good up there. Don't worry, okay?
让我脱了这裤子 去开飞机
Now let's get these pants off and fly some planes.
高手 武器检查
Highball, weapon check now.
收到
Roger that.
- 早上好 费瑞斯先生 - 早上好 各位
- Good morning, Mr. Ferris. - Morning, everybody.
先生们
Gentlemen.
- 就绪了吗 汤姆？ - 是的 费瑞斯先生 准备测试
- We about ready, Tom? - Yes, Mr. Ferris. We are go for test.
蓝宝石 最后一次武器检查
Sapphire, cleared weapons hot at the merge.
费瑞斯测试中心 蓝宝石武器正常
Ferris Test, Sapphire. Weapons are hot.
安全飞行 高手
Fly safe, Highball.
额…不
Um, no.
他娘的 汤姆 它们吃什么长大的？
Goddamn it! Tom, what the hell you feed those things?
F35咯 还能有什么？
F-35s, what else?
醒醒 蓝宝石
Wakey, wakey, Sapphire.
要开火 现在是个好机会
You got a shot, now would be a great time.
放心 高手 正在就位
Easy, Highball. Just lining it up.
我们不可能单独对付它们的
There's no way we're taking these out solo.
快过来 我们想点办法
Get over here. Let's figure something out.
就来 高手
On my way, Highball.
保持方位 飞漂亮点
Now stay right there and look real pretty.
高手 你用你的僚机做诱饵？
Highball, did you just use your wingman as a decoy?
高手 军刀就在你后面 你去哪它们去哪
Highball, those Sabres headed up your 6 can fly anywhere you can.
那咱们去我去不了的地方
Then let's go somewhere I can't fly.
他这是要干嘛？
What the hell is he up to?
去棺材角（飞机失速高度）
Coffin corner.
高手 交战法则设定限高50，000英尺
Highball, rules of engagement set ceiling at 50, 000 feet.
没错 因为再飞高点 军刀会失速 对吗 汤姆？
Yeah, because the Sabres will stall if they go any higher, right, Tom?
你也会失速
And so will you.
压缩机失速 压缩机失速
Compressor stall. Compressor stall.
好！
Yes!
抱歉 他娘的 哈尔
Um, I mean, damn it, Hal.
你的小子工作很执着嘛
Your boy certainly takes his job seriously.
副翼 哈尔 左右摇摆
Ailerons, Hal. Side to side.
知道
I got it.
哈尔
Hal.
替我暖着
Keep it warm for me.
穿过25，000英尺
Going through 25, 000.
你没事吧 高手？
Hey, you okay, Highball?
没事 庆祝一下胜利
Yeah, just taking my victory lap.
- 到达20，000英尺 - 好了 高手 给点反应
- Going through 20, 000. - Okay, Highball, give me some roll.
好棒 爸爸！
Yeah, Dad!
哈尔 听得清楚吗？
Hal, do you read me?
高手 你正在接近弹射极限
Highball, you're approaching minimum ejection altitude.
高手 你已经坠过10，000英尺 失速无法恢复
Highball, you're below 10, 000 AGL. Spin is unrecoverable.
弹射 弹射 弹射！
Eject, eject, eject!
你不害怕吧 爸爸？
You're not scared, are you, Dad?
应该说 我的工作不允许
Let's just say it's my job not to be.
爸爸！
Dad!
你这狗娘养的蠢货！
You stupid son of a bitch. You…
冷静 鲍勃 现在无所谓了
Stand down, Bob. It doesn't matter now.
有所谓
It does matter.
那架崭新的F35坠毁了没关系
Never mind that you crashed a brand-new F-35.
但你破坏了交战规则 你牺牲了你的僚机
You broke the rules of engagement. You sacrificed your wingman.
而且搞砸了整个公司和半个州寄予厚望的合同
And you blew the contract this company was depending on.
抱歉 我以为这是你死我活的
I'm sorry. I thought this was a dogfight.
我一直以为我的目标是胜利
I was under the impression the objective was to win.
目标是为了展示军刀在实战中的表现
No, the objective was to show what the Sabres could do in combat.
实战中 没人会牺牲自己的飞机
And in combat, no pilot is gonna crater his own plane.
我会
I did.
现在你知道应该提高无人机的飞行高限
Now you know you gotta boost the ceiling.
我也展示了它们做不到的
I showed you what they can't do.
你不必在空军军事检察官面前展示这些
You didn't have to make that point in front of Air Force Acquisitions.
够了 凯罗尔
That's enough, Carol.
反正这公司大多数要下岗 你被开除了
Since I'm gonna have to lay off most of my company anyway, you're fired, Hal.
太晚了 卡尔 我辞职
It's too late. I quit.
不能开除他 你也不能辞职
He's not fired and you don't quit.
你被拘禁了 等待调查结果
You're grounded, pending the results of an investigation.
当心身后
Watch your back.
不大会 鲍勃
That's impossible, Bob.
- 告诉我怎么回事？ - 控制锁定了
- Tell me what happened. - Controls locked up.
别胡扯 哈尔 你有机会再点火的
Don't give me that, Hal. You had a window when you could've recovered.
你窒息了？
Did you choke?
你不是第一个出这种事的飞行员 我要知道…
You wouldn't be the first, but I need to know.
控制被锁定了 这到底是怎么回事 嗯？
My controls locked up. What the hell is all this, anyway?
你这身可笑的行头是怎么回事？
What's with the ridiculous suit?
我知道你父亲一直在帮你…
I know your dad's been bucking for you…
这是我职业的选择…
The merits of my career choices…
你是个飞行员 优秀的飞行员
You're a pilot, and a good one.
你在办公室桌上怎么飞
Giving that up to fly a desk is bullshit.
哈尔 我喜欢商务工作 我也很擅长
I like it and I'm good at it.
而且 也不一定我就进不了驾驶舱
Doesn't mean I'll never get in a cockpit again.
这不是非此即彼
It isn't one way or the other.
只有孩子才这么想问题
That's the way a child looks at things,
我们不是孩子了
and we aren't children anymore.
起码…
At least…
我只是不想我在乎的人受伤
I just don't wanna see someone I care about getting hurt.
特别是你
Least of all you.
挑选一个意志
Choose well.
一个测试飞行员的大胆缠斗差点酿成悲剧
A test pilot's daring maneuvers almost ended in tragedy.
目击者称 飞行员哈尔·乔丹在最后一刻弹射跳伞
Witnesses say pilot Hal Jordan ejected at the last possible second…
他的座机坠落在沙漠
before his jet crashed in the open desert.
他的父亲马丁·乔丹…
He's the son of the late Martin Jordan…
在1993年的飞行测试惨剧中丧生
who was killed in his own ill-fated test flight back in 1993.
据说哈尔·乔丹目前状况良好
We are told that Hal Jordan is doing fine right now…
但我们尚未听到任何费瑞斯公司的官方声明
though we have yet to hear an official statement.
嘿 伙计们
Hey, guys.
漏
The incident has been a blow to a new high-tech aircraft program…
工作怎么样？
Hey. How was work?
哇 棒极了 杰克 谢谢关心 嘿 简尼斯
Oh. It was amazing, Jack. Thank you for asking. Hey, Janice.
看看现在的情况 我很想知道
Just help me out here, because I'm really trying to understand this.
你太想学他了 也想和他死得一样？
Do you wanna be like him so bad?
- 你以为是我的失误？ - 我问过卡尔 哈尔
- You just assume it's my fault. - I talked to Carl.
你驾驶飞机到了极限高度…
You pushed the plane past its limits…
那是我的工作 一场事故 大家都没事
That's my job. It was an accident. Everybody walked away.
就像那次摩托车事故让你住了一个月医院吗？
Like your motorcycle accident that put you in the hospital for a month?
我真想念这美好的家庭时光 聊得很愉快 杰克
I miss all this quality family time. Good talk, Jack.
杰森在哪？
Where's Jason?
在他房里
In his room.
怎么了？
Why?
嘿 是我哈尔叔叔
Hey, it's Uncle Hal.
怎么了 王牌飞行员？
What's up there, ace?
这是我参加的最糟的11岁生日聚会
This is the worst 11 th birthday party I've ever been to.
没跳舞的女孩？
No dancing girls? What's going on…
嘿！嘿
Hey.
我没事
I'm fine.
我猜我有点吓坏了
I guess I got a little freaked out or something.
很正常
It happens.
可你不会
Not to you.
听着…
Look…
我告诉过你不必担心
you don't have anything to worry about.
知道为什么吗？
You wanna know why?
也许生活中很多事情我都会搞砸
Yeah, I may be a total screw-up in every other part of my life.
可有件事我很清楚 飞行
But the one thing I do know how to do is fly.
我过去了解这个孩子
You know, I used to know this kid.
他是个有趣的小混蛋
Was a funny-looking little bastard.
有一天 他站在土堆上 掷出了一场完美的比赛
One day, he's standing on the mound, and he throws a perfect game.
他… 他就是我
That… That was me.
是你？
That was you?
还以为很熟悉你呢
Thought you looked familiar.
那天你完全处于巅峰状态 记得吗？
You were totally in the zone that day. Remember?
- 我仍梦见这些 - 我确信
- I still dream about it. - I bet.
带着它
Take it.
闭上你的眼睛
Close your eyes.
继续
Go on.
现在…
Now…
你能精确记起那天你是怎样的感受吗？
can you remember exactly how you felt that day?
在我飞行时就是那种感受
That's how I feel when I'm flying.
就像飞机成为我自身的一部分
Like that plane is a part of me.
不 就像是 不管情况多糟糕…
No, it's like, no matter how bad things get…
总还是有好的一面…
there's something good out there…
仅需越过地平线
just over the horizon.
我真的可以感受到
I could really feel it.
是的
Yeah.
我也是
Me too.
有礼物给你 小寿星 我自己包的
Hey, got you something, birthday boy. Wrapped it myself.
太酷了 这是X-1 对吧？
Cool. It's an X-1, right?
太空战斗机 我爸爸送我的
It's a Starfighter. My dad gave me that.
把它挂起来
Let's put it up.
今天怎么回事？
What happened today?
飞机坠毁的事情
I mean, when you crashed.
我也不太确定
Not really sure, exactly.
你害怕吗？
Were you scared?
不害怕是我的职责
It's my job not to be.
趁你还没错过你超级烂的生日派对
You know, you're totally missing your super-lame birthday party.
赶快去！走 走 走 走 走！
Beat it. Go, go, go!
很高兴你没事
I'm glad you're okay.
我也是 王牌
Me too, ace.
别 别
Get off! No!
别
Aah! No!
千万别死 别死 我找人帮忙
Come on, stay with me. Stay with me. I'm gonna get you some help.
你会没事的 你会没事的 坚持一会
You're gonna be okay. You're gonna be okay. Okay, hold on.
你叫什么？你叫什么？
Your name. Your name.
我叫哈尔 哈尔·乔丹
It's Hal. Hal Jordan.
哈尔·乔丹，我是阿宾·苏尔 2814扇区的守卫者
Hal Jordan, I am Abin Sur, protector of Sector 2814.
嘿嘿嘿 好吧 听着
Okay, hey, listen.
我送你去医院 好吗？
We're gonna get you to a hospital, okay?
好吗？给你输点紫色的血
Okay? One that carries purple blood.
戒指…
The ring…
选中了你
it chose you.
拿着它
Take it!
戴上戒指 放进灯里
Place the ring in the lantern.
戴上戒指 宣读誓言
Place the ring, speak the oath…
- 什么？ - 巨大的荣誉和责任…
- What? - Great honor, responsibility…
我不明白 嘿 继续呼吸 你要呼吸
I don't understand. Breathe. You gotta breathe, okay?
你只需要呼吸 吸气 吸气
All you gotta do is breathe. Just breathe, okay?
嘿 不 不 不 嘿 嘿！
Hey, hey, hey. No, no, no. Hey, hey.
嘿 嘿 嘿 伙计 别这样
Hey, hey, hey. Come on, man. No, no, no, don't do that.
别这样 别…这样
Hey, now, don't do that.
噢 不要啊
Oh, come on.
X-97系统检测完毕
X-97 systems check complete.
喂
Yo.
再说一遍？
Come again?
嗯
Hmm.
太空船？
Is that a spaceship?
没错
Yeah.
真家伙？
Is it real?
真家伙
It's real.
看看动力系统是怎样的？
Did you see what kind of power source this thing uses?
- 看看有什么新发现 - 我们不能留在这儿
- Do you understand… - We can't stay.
- 我们不能留下 - 什么？
- We can't stay here. - What?
- 我们得离开 - 什么？
- Gotta go. - What?
飞行员
Pilot.
他穿着制服 我想他是个战士
He wore a uniform. I think he was a soldier.
他把这个交给了我
He gave me this.
他求婚了？
He proposed?
我们走 我们走！
We're gone. We're gone, now!
他们会知道有人来过
They're gonna know someone was there.
外星飞行员不会把自己埋了
Alien pilots don't bury themselves.
我不能就这样把他留在那
I couldn't just leave him there.
但愿这个东西没辐射
I hope this thing isn't radioactive.
- 你真是个天才！你… - 啊！
- Yeah, well, you're the genius. You… Aah! - Aah!
- 天啊！- 啊！
- Jesus! - Aah! Whoa!
没事
Got it!
他说 是戒指选中了我
He said that the ring chose me.
他说这是莫大的荣耀和责任
He said it was a great honor. Responsibility.
责任？
Responsibility?
- 是的 - 你？
- Yeah. - You?
也许在他们的星球上 责任是混蛋的意思
Well, maybe on their planet "responsibility" just means "asshole."
但愿如此
Let's hope so.
宇宙中一束巨大的光芒熄灭了
A great light has gone out in the universe.
阿宾·苏尔死了
Abin Sur is dead.
4个绿灯兄弟被害
Four of my Lantern brothers killed.
两个星球的居民被未知的敌人灭绝
The inhabitants of two worlds annihilated by an unknown enemy.
一个掌握了黄色恐惧力量的敌人
An enemy that possesses the yellow power of fear.
我们知道它来源于失落的扇区某处
We know it originated from within the Lost Sector.
我们知道 每次遭遇都使其更强大
We know it grows more powerful with each encounter.
根据阿宾·苏尔丢失的讯息 他似乎知道是谁
According to Abin Sur's last transmission, he seemed to know what it was.
他只说了一句话：“是视差怪”
His only words were, "It's Parallax."
我们知道这个危机了 我们正在评估
We are aware of the threat. We are assessing the situation.
你们在评估 无辜的生命却在消逝
While you assess, innocent lives will be lost.
让我向这个新敌人宣战
Let me take the fight to this enemy.
你对他知之甚少 辛纳斯丘
There is much of which you are not aware, Sinestro.
如果这个威胁和我们预料的一样强大…
If the danger is as great as we suspect…
你在说什么？
What are you saying?
你认为他可以打败我们？
You believe this enemy can defeat us?
守卫者们 如果你们的信念有所削弱 让我来提醒你们
Guardians, if your faith in our power has faltered, let me renew it.
让我带一群最强大的军团战士去对抗这个敌人…
Let me take a squadron of my strongest Lanterns against this enemy…
我要向你们证明我们的黄金岁月并未过去
and I'll prove to you our best days are not behind us.
（崛起的新星）
韩蒙德博士？
Dr. Hammond?
哈克特·韩蒙德博士？
Dr. Hector Hammond?
请你跟我们走一趟
We need to ask you to come with us.
是亚当要你们来的？
Did Adam put you up to this?
请下车
Get out of the car, please.
韩蒙德博士？
Dr. Hammond?
我是阿曼达·沃勒博士
Dr. Amanda Waller.
很抱歉如此大动干戈
I must apologize for the theatrics,
可政府有它的做事方式
but the government does like its protocols.
请跟我来
Please, follow me.
不会是真的吧？
Is that what I think it is?
一个外星生命体 博士？
An alien life form, doctor.
人类接触的第一个
The first that mankind has ever encountered…
和阴谋论的说法截然不同
despite what the conspiracy theorists would have you believe.
我们希望你来进行第一次生理分析
We want you to do the initial assessment of its physiology.
我的上帝啊
My God.
为什么是我？
Why me?
作为一个齐诺生物学家 你的能力最适合这个任务
As a xenobiologist, your skills are specifically suited to the task.
此外…
Beyond that…
我只能守口如瓶
I'm not at liberty to tell you.
你好啊
Hello.
眼睛 鼻子 耳和嘴与人类相似
The eyes, nose, ears and mouth are humanoid.
在左前胸区域 有个直径约10厘米…
In the left anterior thoracic region is a 10-centimeter wound…
酸液腐蚀的创口 有紫色凝血
with jagged edges containing attached cyanotic-colored coagulum.
好吧 好了
Okay, all right.
戴上戒指 宣读誓言
Place the ring, then speak the oath.
誓言
The oath.
每个人都知道誓言
Because everybody knows the oath.
训练营里还唱了的
Used to sing it in camp.
我 哈尔·乔丹…
I, Hal Jordan…
庄严宣誓…
do solemnly swear…
宣誓效忠…
to pledge allegiance…
于一盏绿灯…
to a lantern…
一个紫色的外星人弥留之际传给我
that I got from a dying purple alien…
身下一片沼泽
in a swamp.
表皮呈绛红色
The epidermis is magenta.
看上去透明 超薄
It appears transparent and is extremely thin…
可以看到肌肉组织和肌肉纤维
allowing visualization of muscles and individual muscle fibers.
矢志不移
"To infinity and beyond."
灰壳堡赐予我力量吧！（出自《宇宙巨人希曼》）
"By the power of Grayskull."
到底要怎样！
What the hell?!
你能载我飞几百英里然后落在一块荒地上 你难道就…
If you can fly me 100 miles in the middle of nowhere, you'd think that you…
不！
No!
白昼朗朗 黑夜茫茫
In brightest day, in blackest night…
鬼魅魍魉 无所遁藏
no evil shall escape my sight.
邪科奸党 惧吾神光
Let those who worship evil's might…
绿灯长明
beware my power:
万世光芒
Green Lantern's light.
凯罗尔
Carol.
- 一切还好吧？ - 好啊
- Everything okay in there? - It's fine.
我能进来吗？
Well, can I come in?
不行
No.
可以 哦 不行 因为我们… 你想喝一杯吗？
Yeah, no, because we're… Uh, do you wanna get a drink?
- 可以谈谈吗？ - 当然
- Can we talk? - Yeah.
我们谈谈 喝一杯
We can talk and drink.
- 这是我的初步分析 - 谢谢 博士
- My initial analysis. - Thank you, doctor.
我不想再重复一个简单的事实
I don't need to tell you that the mere fact.
它与人类相似 太奇特了
that it's humanoid is extraordinary.
这是一种同向的变异
It's indicating a convergent evolution,
也许有共同的祖先…
or perhaps a common ancestry…
这样的发现真是石破惊天
and the implications of that are staggering.
它来自何方呢？
I mean, where did it come from?
这能彻底改变整个世界审视自己的角度
This could completely change the way that the world views itself.
你能想象公众对此会有什么反应吗？
You imagine the way that the public will react to this?
可我知道这不可能 我知道
Um, but I know that that won't happen. I do.
博士 我和你一样 想要追寻真理
Like yourself, doctor, I'm a seeker of truth.
可资助这个机构的人…
But the people who pay for facilities like this…
有其它的考虑 并贯彻始终
have other priorities and the power to enforce them.
是的 我会保密的
So I keep it a secret.
我们这样的人必须在体制内行事 博士
People like us have to work within the system, doctor.
我们总是尽力而为
We do the best we can.
是的
Right.
把球拿出来
Pick that up.
我…
I, um…
我很抱歉
I'm really sorry.
你还会道歉？
Did you just apologize?
你不是外星人上身了吧？
You haven't been replaced by an alien or something?
不是
No.
我很好
I'm good.
Ah. I'm good.
我很好 好极了 我…
I'm good, totally good. Uh…
你觉得我没有责任感吗？
Do you think I'm irresponsible?
你不用回答 没关系
No need to answer. That's fine.
哈尔
Hal. Ha, ha.
你真漂亮
You look pretty.
我们好久没来这里了 自从…
And we haven't been in this place together since…
那天晚上
that night.
- 你忘记了我的生日 - 有吗？
- You forgot it was my birthday. - Did I?
是的
Mm.
也是在那一晚 我们第一次…
That was also the night… The first time that we ever…
一起飞行
flew together.
之后你一直在飞行 搭档换了又换
You've been flying ever since with anyone who'd get in the plane.
喔 不错
Oh, yeah.
- 不 - 来吧
- Oh, no. - Come on.
来吧 我们走
No, yeah, let's go.
- 陪我跳舞吧 - 不
- Dance with me. - No.
不跳
No.
哈尔 不跳
Hal. No.
不跳
No.
我真的很抱歉
I really am sorry.
没关系 合约不是完全没希望
Oh. It's okay. The contract isn't quite dead yet.
我告诉过你我不擅长这个
I told you I was good at this.
我不是说的合约
I wasn't talking about the contract.
我说我们的分开 你明白吗？
I would've screwed this up. You know?
就算我没加入空军…
Even if I didn't go to the Air Force…
我也会以某种方式…
I would've found some way to…
搞砸我们的关系
You and me, I would've blown it.
你是这么对自己说的？
Yeah, is that what you tell yourself?
你怎么对自己说的？
Mm. What do you tell yourself?
你害怕我们太过亲近
That you were scared I was getting too close.
你知道我整个下午在干嘛？
You know what I spent my afternoon doing?
干嘛？
What?
担心你
Worrying about you.
我仔细看过飞行记录
I went over every inch of the flight data.
飞机是没有任何问题的
There was nothing wrong with the plane.
- 当时发生什么事了？ - 谢谢跟我跳舞
- What happened up there? - Thanks for the dance.
我跟你说过当心背后 乔丹
I told you to watch your back.
你让我们都失业了 你这狗娘养的
You cost us all our jobs, you son of a bitch.
可悲
Pathetic.
你这杂种一辈子都活在你父亲的光环下
Bastard's been living off his old man's reputation his whole life.
嘿
Hey.
嘿！
Hey!
我的脸才刚刚热呢
My face is just getting warmed up.
自我欣赏结束了吗？
Have you concluded admiring yourself?
哦 是的
Uh…
嗯 你的戒指翻译功能还不错
Well, your ring translator is functioning properly.
需要身份保密的时候 你的面罩就会出现
Your mask will appear when protection of your identity is required.
在欧阿星上就不需要了
There is no need for it on Oa.
你是一条会说话的鱼
A talking fish.
我是祖达里安人
Actually, my race is Xudarian.
我们的基因确与你们的鱼类生物相似
Our DNA does somewhat resemble your own ichthyological species.
我们是托马·雷 2813扇区的守卫者
I am Tomar-Re, protector of Sector 2813 and home to…
包含80，012个银河系 234万种已知生物
80, 012 galaxies, 2.34 million sentient species.
我怎么会知道这些？
How do I know that?
是知识植入
The induction process.
它能开启戒指的高级功能
It activates the ring's higher functions,
包括有效知识库
including a working knowledge base.
其实 我们很奇怪
In truth, we were curious.
挑选程序从未作用于人类这么年轻的种族
The process had never been attempted on a species as young as humans before.
你是第一个被选中的人类 我被派来迎接你
As you are the first to be chosen, I've been sent to welcome you here.
这里是？
And here is?
欢迎来到欧阿行星
Welcome to Oa.
无数年来 这里一直是我们的家
This planet has been our home for countless millennia.
由守卫者为我们创造
It was created for us by the Guardians.
守卫者？
Guardians?
他们站在圣殿上
There stands their Citadel.
他们是远古种族中的不朽者
They are immortals, among the most ancient of races.
他们创造了这一切 负责我们的存在与言行
They made all you see and are responsible for all we are and do.
远古时期 绿灯军团就是…
Since time immemorial, the Green Lantern Corps…
宇宙和平、秩序和正义的守卫者
has served as the keepers of peace, order and justice throughout the universe.
被选中加入其中 是莫大的荣耀…
To be chosen to join its ranks is the highest of honors…
也是莫大的责任
and the greatest of responsibilities.
嗯 这话我听过
Yeah. Yeah, that part I heard about.
我们现在开始飞行
We're going to fly now.
- 飞行？ - 当然
- Fly? - Absolutely.
好吧
All right.
我能飞的
I can do that.
来吧
Join me.
我能飞的
I can do that.
那是什么？
What is that?
那是中央能量池产生的能量
It's the energy that's generated from the Central Battery.
它的能量来自于宇宙中所有生物的意志
Its power comes from the will of every living creature in the universe.
它为你的灯提供能量 灯为戒指提供能量
It, in turn, charges your lantern, which, in turn, charges your ring.
你的衣服也是纯粹的能量
Even your suit is comprised entirely of energy.
为什么都是绿色的？
What's with all the green?
绿色是意志的颜色
Green is the color of will.
守卫者利用意志…
The Guardians harnessed will…
因为它是宇宙间最强大的力量
because it's the strongest source of energy in the universe.
好多成员
There's so many.
在晴朗的夜晚 你在母星上看能到的星球…
The stars you can see from your home planet on the clearest night…
只是你扇区的千分之一
your sector is a thousand times larger.
3600盏灯各对应一个扇区 亦同样大
And 3600 Lanterns, each with a sector just as vast.
绿灯战士们 我召集你们来参加这次前所未有的聚会
Lanterns, I've called you here to this unprecedented gathering…
因为我们正面临前所未有的威胁
because we face an unprecedented danger.
4位绿灯同袍已被害 凶手就是视差怪
Our four Lantern brothers were killed by an enemy called Parallax.
一个我们尚未完全了解的敌人
An enemy we don't yet fully understand.
但我们知道 它已强大到彻底摧毁一个文明
We do know it's powerful enough to destroy entire civilizations.
强大到 能打败阿宾·苏尔…
Powerful enough to defeat even Abin Sur…
我们最精英的战士
our finest warrior…
他的存在无人可替代
whose light can never be replaced.
守卫者们命令我带领我们最强大的战士…
The Guardians have charged me to lead a squadron of Lanterns…
去进攻视差怪
in an assault on Parallax.
我们会搜索并找到这个强敌
We will seek out and find this enemy.
我们将打败它
And we will destroy it.
单体 我们是脆弱的
Alone, we are now vulnerable.
团结 我们仍然无坚不摧
United, we are still invincible.
我们从未失利过
We have never been defeated.
现在会失利吗？
Will we be defeated now?
不！
No!
我们的存在就是为了这一刻
It was for this moment that we were created.
我不必再赘述你们的职责
But I don't need to tell you your duty.
我不必再赘述我们是谁
I don't need to tell you who we are.
绿灯军团！绿灯军团！
We are the Corps! We are the Corps!
你的意志能将想象变成现实
Your will turns thought into reality.
要支配你的戒指 你必须集中你的意志
To master the ring, you must learn to focus your will…
将脑中幻想变为现实
and create what you see in your mind.
戒指的极限 就是你想象的极限
The ring's limits are only what you can imagine.
再来一次
Do that again.
现在你试试
Now you try.
集中注意力
Concentrate.
有外来威胁 戒指会发出警告
The ring will inform you where there is an imminent threat.
这次的威胁名叫基洛沃格
This particular threat's name is Kilowog.
他是你的格斗教官
He'll be your combat training officer.
- 哇！- 绝不要放松警惕 废物
- Whoa! - Never let your guard down, poozer.
欢迎来到101摔打场
Welcome to Ring Slinging 101.
或者 如我常说的
Or as I like to call it:
你黯淡生命的最糟一天
The worst day of your worthless life.
人类 以前从来没见过
The human. Ain't never seen one before.
- 你闻起来好怪 - 呃
- You smell funny. - Ugh.
我闻起来好怪？
I smell funny?
我听说过人类自以为是宇宙的中心
Yeah, I heard about humans. Think you're the center of the universe.
你想做绿灯战士？
You want to be a Lantern?
你就得献身军团
You gotta commit to the Corps.
好吧 废物 看看你有什么能耐
All right, poozer. Let's see what you've got.
你的创造只会和你的意志一样弱
Your constructs are only gonna be as strong as your will.
你的意志弱的可怜
And your will is pathetic.
看我整你 我会一直打击你…
I'm gonna work you and I'm gonna hit you…
直到你的意志配得上绿灯军团
until your will is strong enough to be worthy of the Corps.
下一课
Next lesson.
哈哈 有感觉吗？
Ha, ha. Feel that?
这是普通恒星的引力
It's the gravitational pull of your average sun.
因此太空飞行非常危险
Makes flying through space very dangerous.
个头越大 引力越大
The bigger you are, the quicker you burn.
引力是个贱人
Gravity's a bitch.
来吧 拉你起来
Here, let me help you.
记住 你的敌人不会手软
Remember, your enemy, he's not gonna play fair.
嗯 这建议不错 谢了 美人
Well, that's good advice. Thanks, gorgeous.
原来如此
So…
你就是那个人类
this is the human.
当我听说阿宾·苏尔的戒指选中了你…
When I learned Abin Sur's ring had chosen you…
我说它一定是搞错了
I said there had to be a mistake.
看来确实如此
I see nothing to change my mind.
基洛沃格 我来接手
I'll take it from here, Kilowog.
军团的力量取决于其最弱的一环
The Corps is only as strong as its weakest link.
我不会容忍弱者
And I will tolerate no weak links.
你明白吗？
You understand me?
你害怕了 人类？
Are you afraid, human?
你害怕吗？
Are you afraid?
别
Don't.
不要这样
Don't do that.
切磋下？
Shall we?
来吧
Sure.
剑？
A sword?
这就是人类
How human.
我确信我闻到了恐惧的味道
I do believe I smell fear.
我是绿灯战士
I'm a Green Lantern.
我无所畏惧
I fear nothing.
畏惧是意志的敌人
Fear is the enemy of will.
意志使你采取行动
Will is what makes you take action.
畏惧会阻止你 让你软弱
Fear is what stops you and makes you weak.
让你创造无力
Makes your constructs feeble.
你必须抛开畏惧 你恐惧 就无法行动
You must ignore your fear. When you're afraid, you can't act.
无法行动就无法自卫 无法自卫 就死路一条
When you can't act, you can't defend. If you can't defend, you die.
你的恐惧恶臭扑鼻 哈尔·乔丹
You reek of fear, Hal Jordan.
阿宾·苏尔是位伟大的战士
Abin Sur was a great warrior.
我的导师
My mentor.
我的挚友
My friend.
你戴着他的戒指 侮辱了他的声誉
You insult his memory by wearing his ring.
我不干了 他说得对 我只是个人类
I'm done. He's right. I'm only human.
我们没准备好去保卫宇宙
We're not ready to defend the universe.
几天前我还以为宇宙里只有人类
A few days ago, we thought we were the only ones in the universe.
戒指选中了你 你一定有过人之处
The ring chose you. It wouldn't have if it hadn't seen something in you.
真的吗？
Oh, yeah?
连你自己都未曾意识到
Something you yourself don't yet see.
戒指从不选错人
The ring never makes a mistake.
这次它错了
This time it did.
（科学楼）
直到最近 我们才发现…
That until recently, we didn't realize…
许多被我们一直称为细菌的小生物其实不是细菌
that many of these little critters that we've been calling bacteria weren't bacteria at all.
它们是原始的原核细胞生物
They were an entirely different type of primitive prokaryotic cell.
这些称为“古生菌”的小虫子并不为人所知
These little buggers, called archaeans, are still poorly understood.
也许与细菌截然不同…
But might turn out to be different from bacteria…
也许与我们所谓的细菌截然不同
But might turn out to be as different from bacteria as bacteria is from us.
有些人称它们为“嗜极菌”
Some call them extremophiles…
因为它们生存在地球上极端的环境中 比如…
because they live in the most extreme environments on Earth, such as…
天啊 太无聊了
God, he's so boring.
温泉的沸水里
The boiling waters of a geyser.
看他耸样
What a loser.
- 迈克尔？ - 嗯？
- Michael! - Huh?
你刚才说什么？
What did you say?
我什么也没说啊
I didn't say anything.
你说我耸样？
Did you just call me a loser?
这家伙是什么怪物？
What kind of freak is this guy?
怪物？
"Freak"?!
下课！
Class dismissed.
（下午3点到我办公室 爸爸）
你怎么样？
So how you been?
好久不见了
Been a while.
昨晚很激烈吧 她叫什么 嗯？
So you had a rough night last night. Did you get her name, huh?
你睡眠不好啊 儿子
You need to get some sleep, son.
- 坐吧 - 叫我来什么事 爸爸？
- Have a seat. - What can I do for you, Dad?
其实 你已经做过的事
Well, actually, you've already done it.
为了我 为了国家
For me and for your country.
你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
我在说 你给很多重量级人物留下了很深的印象
I'm talking about you impressing a whole lot of very important people.
你怎么会有这个？
Where did you get that?
我在一个监管政府机构的下属委员会
I'm on a subcommittee overseeing the agencies involved.
- 绝密 当然 - 是因为你 他们才选我
- Top-secret, of course. - It was you. That's why they chose me.
有了这个 你将得到内部的高级职位…
Because of this, we're gonna be able to get you a top post on the inside now…
协助监管整个工程
helping to oversee the operation.
有些科学家为此工作了一辈子
There are scientists that worked their whole lives for this.
- 嗯 - 更优秀的科学家
- Mm-hm. - People more qualified.
却没什么社会关系
And less connected.
别天真了 孩子 世界就是如此
Don't be naive, son. It's the way the world works.
机会出现时 你一定要抓住
You have to seize an opportunity when it presents itself.
他搞不成的
He'll never get it.
浪费生命
Just wasting his life away.
真让人难堪
What an embarrassment.
比尔！你好吗？
Bill! Ha. How are you?
我好极了
I'm terrific.
不 不 不 刚结束一个会 有很多时间
No, no, no. Just finishing up a meeting. Got plenty of time.
（2312扇区 银河边缘）
我亲眼看到这个怪物诱导我最精英的战士恐惧缠身…
With my own eyes I saw this creature induce fear in our finest warriors…
并吞噬了他们的恐惧
and then feed on that fear.
还有
There's more.
我们跟踪了他的轨迹 他正向欧阿星进发
We've tracked its trajectory. Parallax is headed for Oa.
从未有谁胆敢进攻我们
Never before has an enemy dared attack us here.
你们必须告诉我你知道什么
You must tell me what you know.
意志一直是我们唯一的武器…
Will has always been our sole weapon…
来对抗宇宙中的黑暗力量
against the forces of darkness in the universe.
可当这个力量还不够时…
But as that power began to seem insufficient…
我们中间产生了激烈争论
a great debate arose among us.
我们是否应该利用新的力量源…
Should we exploit another source of power…
我们发誓永不使用的？
one we had long since sworn should never be used?
恐惧
Fear.
恐惧的力量太难以预测
But the power of fear was too unpredictable.
受腐蚀的风险太高
The chance of corruption too great.
因此我们决定弃用
And so we decided against it.
但有一个人除外
All of us, that is, except one.
这个守卫者一个人进入了禁殿
Alone, this Guardian entered the forbidden chamber.
他想证明恐惧的光芒也是可以被控制的
He wanted to prove the light of fear could be mastered.
他的出发点是单纯的…
His intentions were pure…
愿望却是幼稚的
but his hopes were naive.
这名守卫者被黄色的恐惧力量吞噬…
Consumed by the yellow power of fear…
变成了我们要消灭的敌人
the Guardian became the very evil he had wished to destroy.
他变成了视差怪
He became Parallax.
为了宇宙和他自己的安危…
For the universe's safety and his own…
阿宾·苏尔被派去失落的扇区囚禁视差怪
Abin Sur was charged with imprisoning Parallax in the Lost Sector.
但它逃走了
But he escaped.
吸取了别人的恐惧 使他越来越大 越来越强壮
Feeding on the fear of others, he grew larger, more powerful.
他正向这里赶来…
And is now headed here…
向你们复仇 消灭绿灯军团
to take his revenge on you and destroy the Corps.
如此 我们别无选择
Then we have no choice.
我们必须准备利用敌人的力量 用恐惧对抗恐惧
We must prepare to harness the power of our enemy and fight fear with fear.
要保卫我们的扇区 我们首先要保卫自己
To protect our sectors, we must be able to defend ourselves.
我们必须铸造一个黄色戒指
We must forge a yellow ring.
小心走路
Watch your step.
参议员
Senator.
不用再为我担心
Don't have to worry about me no more.
我已经离开
I'm gone.
已离开 已离开
I'm gone, I'm gone.
你好
Hello.
嗨
Hi.
大家站起身
Everybody get on your feet.
你们坐着我就紧张
You make me nervous When you're in your seat.
难过的夜晚 嗯？
Rough night, huh?
哈克特
Hector.
你还吗？最近忙什么？
How you doing? What have you been up to?
- 老样子 老样子 - 我也是
- Same old, same old. - Yeah. Me too.
哈尔·乔丹 最糟的飞行员 或者最棒的 不太确定
Hal Jordan. Worst pilot I've ever seen. Or the best. Not quite sure.
说什么的都有
I've been called both.
很高兴你来 孩子
Glad you could make it, son.
收到邀请我很意外
I was a little surprised I got the invite.
一家人 哈尔
No, you're family, Hal.
他们说 这世界上有思想者 有行动者
There are thinkers in this world and there are doers.
你就是个行动者
And you are one of the doers.
是的 可思想者使我的行动成为可能
Yeah, but the thinkers make what I do possible.
没人事先设计 就不会有飞机
Wouldn't have a plane unless someone thought it up.
当然
Of course.
抱歉 我要去喝一杯
Excuse me, I need a drink.
- 我要去工作了 这就是工作 - 是的 先生
- I gotta get back to work. This is work. - Yes, sir.
- 很高兴见到你 孩子 - 我也是
- Nice to see you, son. - You too. You too.
不错啊
Nice.
嗯 我爸爸以前在这上面受训
Yeah, my dad used to train in it.
我说你的裙子
I was talking about your dress.
西装不错
Nice jacket.
上次我看的时候 你还没有西装的
Last time I checked, you didn't even own one.
我最近在整理衣柜
Yeah, I've been shaking up the wardrobe lately.
恭喜你们拿到合同了 你怎么办到的？
Congratulations on the contract. How'd you manage to pull that off?
我跟他们说 你破坏了交战规则才赢的
I pointed out you only won because you broke the rules of engagement.
汤姆在考虑增加军刀的飞行高度极限
And Tom figured out how to give the Sabres more altitude.
因此我猜 也许非本意 你以某种方式…
So I guess in a way, without even meaning to…
帮了我们一把
you actually did us a favor.
听着…
Look…
“英雄”这次词让我难受
I'm uncomfortable with the word "hero."
谢谢 谢谢大家的光临
Thank you. Thank you all for joining us.
精彩的夜晚
Great evening.
有个很特别的人我想感谢 帮我们拿到了合同
Somebody very special I'd like to thank for helping us to nail this contract:
我的女儿 凯罗尔·费瑞斯
My daughter, Carol Ferris.
来吧！
Come on!
恭喜 凯罗尔！
Congratulations, Carol.
我看着你 年轻的女士…
I take one look at you, young lady…
或者站在那里的哈尔·乔丹 如乃父在世…
or at Hal Jordan over there, spitting image of his dad…
- 哇哦！- 你们就是希望
- Whoo! - You give us hope.
为我们的未来干杯
A toast to our future.
- 听着 听着！ - 为未来干杯！
- Hear, hear! - To the future!
我们后继有人
We're in good hands.
哈克特！噢 天啊！嘿！
Hector! Oh, my God! Hey!
- 恭喜… - 谢谢
- Congratulations. Um… - Thank you.
敬你和哈尔 我们的未来
Here's to you and Hal, the future.
哦 抱歉
Yeah, heh, I'm sorry.
我知道和你父亲一起 成长是艰难的
I know it couldn't have been easy growing up with your dad.
不过 你也干得不错啊…
But, hey, you're doing great, so… Ha, ha.
是的 我干得不错
I am. I'm doing great. Ha, ha.
- 不过他说的对 我不是个行动者 - 哈哈
- He's right, though. I'm not a doer. - Ha, ha.
不过我最近有机会检验了一个外星人尸体
Although I did get to examine an alien body recently.
太酷了
That was very cool.
我不能告诉外人 不过 你不能…
I can't tell anyone about it, but, hey, you can't have everything.
你又在讲你的科幻故事了？
Hector telling you another of his science-fiction stories?
他是怎么回事？
What the hell's wrong with him?
不知道何时该闭嘴吗？
Can't keep his mouth shut.
你确实很有想象力
You really do have a creative imagination.
再见
Bye.
参议员
Senator.
抱歉 我们必须走了
I apologize. We really must go.
- 晚安 凯罗尔 - 晚安
- Good night, Carol. - Good night.
参议员
Senator!
嘿
Hey.
谢谢啦
Thanks for everything.
再见 参议员
Bye, senator!
叫急救队来 我们的直升飞机要坠毁了
Get the crash crew here. Our helicopter's going down.
噢 天啊
Oh, my God.
那是什么？
What is that? What is that?
今晚发生的事情只在数秒之间…
What happened tonight took place in just a matter of seconds…
可人们会谈论好多年
but people will be talking about it for years to come.
一架直升飞机失控 险酿惨剧…
A helicopter careening out of control, headed toward certain tragedy…
突然间 一个神秘男子 一个英雄 拯救了大家…
when all of a sudden, a mystery man, a hero, saves the day…
避免了飞机冲进人群…
incredibly diverting the helicopter from destroying innocent people…
奇迹般地拯救了凯罗尔·费瑞斯
and miraculously rescuing Carol Ferris.
关键是这位英雄是谁 他在哪？
The real question tonight is who is this amazing hero and where is he now?
老实交代
Start talking.
- 赛车道？ - 对啊
- A racetrack? - Yeah.
你的第一次亮相 你最拿手的就是赛车道？
That's the best you could come up with for your first big appearance? Racetrack.
噢 抱歉 我让你失望了？
Oh, I'm sorry. Did I disappoint you?
我用纯能量制造了一个赛车道
I materialized a track out of pure energy,
救了几百号人 你居然失望了
saving hundreds, and you're disappointed.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry about that.
不 我想看看 展示一下
No, I wanna see this stuff. Show me.
我想 不太好吧
I don't think that's a good idea.
来吧 给我看看
Come on, I wanna see this stuff.
我要看行头 飞行什么的 你得给我看看
I wanna see the outfit, the flying… You gotta show me.
哈尔 做你最好的朋友可不容易
Hal, being your best friend's no picnic.
- 紧急情况下才用的！ - 你欠我的！
- It's for emergencies! - You owe me!
哈尔 我想看看
Hal, I wanna see it.
好吧
Fine.
戴好你的眼镜
Hold on to your glasses.
好的
All right.
提问：
Question:
- 准备好灵魂出窍了？ - 是的
- You ready to have your mind blown? - Yeah.
戒指
Ring.
手指
Finger.
来吧
Here we go.
- 你是不是把戒指弄坏了？ - 我没弄坏 好吧 只是…
- Did you break it already? - I didn't break it, okay? It's just…
没水了 得充一点
It's out of juice. I have to recharge it.
现在注意了
Now pay attention.
啊！绿的！
Aah! Green!
- 哇噢 - 我说 不是吗？
- Wow. - I know, right?!
不错吧 嗯？
Not bad, huh?
你是超级英雄了
You're a superhero.
不是应该有个妞的吗？
Don't they always get the girl?
晚上好 女士
Evening, ma'am.
还未有机会跟你道别
Didn't get a chance to say goodbye.
你没事吧？
Are you okay?
是的 没事 很高兴有机会能谢谢你
Uh, yeah, no, I'm glad to have a chance to thank you.
是我应该做的 不必谢我 小姐
Just doing my job. No thanks necessary, miss.
应该谢的
No, it is.
你救了我的命
You saved my life.
你救了我们大家的命 实在…
You saved all of our lives. That was a very…
哈尔？
Hal?
女士？
Miss?
哈尔？！
Hal?!
我的天… 天啊！
Oh, my Go… Oh, my God!
- 我的天啊 哈尔！ - 你怎么知道是我？
- Oh, my God! Hal! - How did you know it was me?
什么意思？我认识你一辈子了！没穿衣服我都见过！
What? I've known you my whole life! I've seen you naked!
你以为穿了马甲 我就认不出你了？
You don't think I would recognize you because I can't see your cheekbones?!
怎么回事？你怎么变绿了？还在发光？
What is this?! Why is your skin green? Why are you glowing?
怎么还戴个面具？
What the hell is with that mask?!
这是行头的一部分
It came with the outfit.
酷吧 嗯？
Cool, huh?
这一切都因为这枚魔法戒指？
So it all works because of this magic ring? Ha, ha.
不 不是什么魔法
No, there's no such thing as magic.
银河绿色维和部队 有几千人
Intergalactic green peacekeepers, thousands of them.
但是 不
But, no.
我不是瞎编的
I'm not making it up.
我们小时候 谁会想到呢？
I mean, when we were kids, who'd have thought?
- 我想过的 真的 我一直期待着 - 哈哈哈
- I did, actually. I called this early on. - Ha-ha-ha.
我说：“有一天 我要成为绿色的太空警察” 我成功了
I said, "One day I'll be a green space cop." Here I am.
那天在晚会上 怎么弄出的那个绿色的车道的？
Okay, so at the party, how did you make that big green ramp thing?
我脑子里想什么 就能创造出来 只需集中注意力
Anything I see in my mind, I can create. I just have to focus.
什么都行？
Anything?
什么都行
Anything.
生日快乐 迟到好过没有
Happy birthday. Better late than never.
你们怎么工作的？
Okay, so how does it work?
他们打你手机 然后说
They just, um, call you on your cell,
“天灵灵 地灵灵”？
"Cat in a tree, downtown Milky Way"?
不 我想可不是那样的
No. I don't think it works exactly like that.
这个 纯技术角度说 嗯…
Well, technically speaking, um…
其实我 嗯…
I actually sort of, uh…
退出了
quit.
什么意思？怎么退出？
What do you mean? How?
这个 意思是 和退出其它事情一样
Well, I mean, it's a lot like quitting anything else, really.
我不明白
I don't understand.
怎么连这样的事情你也会放弃？
How do you walk away from something like that?
这可能吗？
Is that even possible?
我想我们都很清楚 我很擅长放弃
Oh, I think we both know I'm pretty good at walking away.
哪怕一次 你不退出你喜欢的事情…
If for once you didn't quit something you cared about…
最差又能怎样呢？
what's the worst that could happen?
谢谢你 今晚很特别
Well, thank you. This has been really something.
我知道我犯了很多错误…
I know I've made a lot of mistakes…
哈尔 我不是生你的气
Look, Hal, I'm not mad at you.
我只是替你难过 真的
I feel bad for you, really.
你放弃了这么多 都成了习惯
You've been given so much so often.
而你…
And you just…
晚安
Good night.
韩蒙德博士？
Dr. Hammond?
有些东西我想给你看看
There is something I'd like to show you.
我很肯定 你想看的
Something I'm fairly certain you'll want to see.
再见 妈妈
See you later, Mom.
- 我爱你 - 再见 宝贝
- I love you. - Bye, baby.
不！
No!
实体接触便可进入记忆系统
Physical contact accesses mnemonic data.
我能看到你的记忆
I can see your memories.
爸爸
Dad.
儿子 都是我的错
Son, this is my fault.
不过我会弥补的
But I'm gonna fix it.
我们会让你好起来 不惜一切代价
We're gonna get you well again. Whatever it takes.
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
我们检测到了第二种外星生命体…
We detected traces of a second alien life form…
埋藏在第一个的体内
buried within the body of the first.
你被感染了
You've been exposed.
我这辈子从未如此爽过
I've never felt better in my life.
我们都知道了 儿子
We know everything, son.
我这辈子从未如此爽过
I've never felt better in my life.
被选中加入其中 是莫大的荣耀…
To be chosen to join its ranks is the highest of honors…
也是莫大的责任
and the greatest of responsibilities.
戒指从不犯错
The ring never makes a mistake.
一切都会好的
It's gonna be all right.
他们只需要做些检查 如此而已
They just need to run some tests, that's all.
让他保持昏迷
Keep him under.
我都是为了你好
I only want what's best for you.
快跑
Run.
- 哈克特 - 嘘 嘘
- Hector. - Shh, shh.
别担心
Don't worry.
我都是为了你好
I only want what's best for you.
戒指 它选中了你
The ring, it chose you.
拿着它！
Take it!
哈尔
Hal.
嗨
Hi.
那个外星人是你们的人
The alien was one of you.
为什么我们如此不同？
How did we end up so different?
嗯？嗯？
Hmm? Hmm?
坐下！
Sit down!
我问你…
Now…
凯罗尔怎么样？
how's Carol?
- 不该那样的 - 算了
- That came out wrong. - Please.
- 我犯了很多错… - 听着 哈尔…
- I've made mistakes… - Look, Hal…
我替你感到难过 真的 晚安
I feel bad for you, really. Good night.
你和我一样是悲剧
You're just as much of a failure as I was.
一样害怕
And just as afraid.
好吧…
Well…
我一直在反抗恐惧
I used to fight my fear.
现在我才尝到它真实的力量…
But now that I've tasted its true power…
我不会再回头了
I'll never go back.
不！
No!
你戴的绿灯戒指曾经囚禁了我
You wear the ring of the Lantern that imprisoned me.
你也会遭受同样的命运
You will suffer the same fate.
我曾经吞吃了你们的世界…
Once I have devoured your world…
我已经获得足够的力量…
I will have all the strength I need…
打败绿灯军团 消灭守卫者
to defeat the Corps and destroy the Guardians.
让我搞清楚
Let me get this straight.
在那里攻击行星的东西和哈克特有关？
This thing that's out there attacking planets is connected to Hector?
它杀了阿宾·苏尔后感染了他
Somehow it infected him after it killed Abin Sur.
你必须要阻止它
Well, you're just gonna have to stop it.
哦 我必须要阻止它 嗯？
Oh, I'm just gonna have to stop it, huh?
我试过 我失败了
Well, I tried that and I failed.
参议员死了 我告诉你 戒指选错人了
And the senator died. I told you, the ring made a mistake.
等等 往后倒 戒指怎么选错人了？
Wait, go back. How did the ring make a mistake?
绿灯战士唯一的要求就是“无畏”
The one thing that a Green Lantern is supposed to be is fearless.
工作内容就是“无畏”
Fearless is the job description.
我不是那样的
That isn't me.
所以你这次又要一走了之？
So you're just gonna walk away again?
解释一下 哈尔 请解释一次给我听听 为什么？
Explain this to me, Hal. Please explain to me just once, why.
因为我害怕
Because I'm afraid!
你以为你爸爸就从不害怕吗？
You don't think your dad ever felt afraid?
即使他害怕 他也有办法克服它
If he did, he figured out some way to beat it.
是的 克服它就一个词：
Yeah, well, there's a word for that:
勇气
Courage.
他们说 如果没有过人之处 戒指是不会选我的
They said that the ring wouldn't have chosen me if it didn't see something.
可我还没看到
Something I don't see. Yet.
我看到了
I see it.
我一直都能看到
I always have.
戒指没看到你的无畏
The ring didn't see that you were fearless.
它看到了你可以克服恐惧
It saw that you had the ability to overcome fear.
它看到了你的勇气
It saw that you're courageous.
你有的
Which you are.
和你爸爸一样
Just like your dad.
绿灯侠是个威胁
The Lantern is a threat.
消灭他
Eliminate him.
我们的新武器造好了
Our new weapon is ready.
一旦我掌握了它的力量…
Once I've mastered its power…
我会训练其他人效仿
I'll begin training the Corps to do the same.
虽然地球会被毁灭…
Though Earth will be lost…
视差怪到达欧阿行星之前 我们会准备好对抗它
we'll be ready to make a stand against Parallax before it reaches Oa.
敌人的力量将为我们所用
Then the power of the enemy will be ours.
代价呢？
At what cost?
- 你胆敢进入圣殿？ - 我需要你的帮助
- You dare enter this chamber? - I need your help.
你要帮助我拯救我的世界
You gotta help me save my world.
我知道人类不是最强壮 最聪明的物种
I know that humans aren't the strongest species, or the smartest.
我们年轻 我们还有很多要学的
We're young, we have a lot to learn.
可我们值得被拯救
But we're worth saving.
新武器 你不能使用
This new weapon of yours, you can't use it.
一旦你越过了界限 屈服于恐惧
Once you cross that line, once you've given in to fear,
你无法回头 我见识过
you'll never go back. I've seen it.
听着 我知道你们现在害怕
Look, I know right now you're afraid.
你胆敢指责守卫者害怕？
You dare accuse the Guardians of feeling fear?
是的
Yes, I do.
这就是为什么视差怪能打败你们…
That's exactly why Parallax is beating you…
因为你们害怕承认害怕
because you're afraid to even admit you're afraid.
我知道
I know.
我这一辈子都是这样
I spent my entire life doing it.
我们在地球上有句话
You know, we have a saying on Earth.
我们说：“我只是个普通人”
We say, "I'm only human."
这么说是因为我们脆弱
We say it because we're vulnerable,
这么说是因为我们知道我们害怕
we say it because we know we're afraid.
但并不意味着我们好欺负
It doesn't mean we're weak.
帮我拯救我的星球
Help me save my planet.
不要屈从于恐惧
Don't give in to fear.
打败它 和我一起打败它
Fight it. Fight it with me.
你的话让人动容 年轻的人类
Your words are compelling, young human.
可做为不朽者 我们要以几十亿年的眼光来衡量我们的行为…
But as immortals, we must measure our actions over billions of years…
以及宇宙的命运
and the fate of the universe.
我们不可能赌上一切 来指望你是对的
We simply cannot risk losing everything on the chance you might be right.
不要 不要赌上更多的生命
Then don't. Don't risk any more lives.
只是我的
Just mine.
让我去为我的世界抗争…
Let me go fight for my world…
我会证明 意志比恐惧要强大
and I'll show you that will is stronger than fear.
你不可能成功的
There is no way you can succeed.
你会死的 哈尔·乔丹
You will die, Hal Jordan.
死得其所
Then I'll die trying.
祝你好运 绿灯侠
Good luck, Green Lantern.
不要轻举妄动
I wouldn't do that.
你仔细看
Look closely.
她真美 是吗？
She's beautiful, isn't she?
我对她一见倾心
I loved her from the moment I first saw her.
可她永远也瞧不上我 就因为你
But she could never see me, as you were always standing in the way.
但以后不会了
But not anymore.
不 不 别 别 别这样 哈克特
No! No! Don't! Don't do this, Hector.
求你
Please.
我知道你的感受
I know how you feel.
得了吧 你看看你自己！
Come on, look at yourself!
真的 我知道…
No, I know what it's like…
总是让人失望…
to not live up to expectations…
做什么都不对
to feel like nothing that you do will ever be good enough.
我知道恐惧是什么感觉
I know what it's like to be afraid.
让我来帮你
Let me help you.
哈尔 你变了
Hal. You've changed.
太棒了 世界末日了才能让你成熟起来
How wonderful that all it took for you to grow up was the end of the world.
现在轮到我了
Now it's my turn.
如果我不能变成你 我就让她变成我
And if I can't be like you, I'm gonna make her like me.
面对现实吧 如果她变成我这样…
And let's face it, once she's like me…
你就没什么兴趣了
then you wouldn't be very interested.
嗯？对不对？
Hmm? Now, would you?
- 你为什么不行？ - 嗯？
- Why can't you? - Hmm?
你为什么不能变成我这样？
Why can't you be like me?
放开她…
Let her go…
你就能得到它
and you can have it.
你可以为所欲为
You can do anything.
无所不能
Be anything.
拿去吧
Take it.
让她来选择
Let her make the choice.
好吧
Okay.
现在放她下来
Now bring her down.
哈尔
Hal.
我骗你的
I lied.
我也是骗你的
I lied too.
规矩是…
See, the way it works is…
你得被选中
you have to be chosen.
你真让我失望
You have failed me.
待在这里
Stay here.
没问题
No problem.
你的意志很强大 可不够强大
Your will is strong, but not strong enough.
没了戒指 你什么都不是
You are nothing without the ring.
你们必须离开这个区域
You must move out of the area now.
街道疏散
Please clear the streets.
街道立刻疏散
Clear the streets immediately.
你打不过它的 你会死的
You can never beat this. You'll die.
至少我可以带它离开这里
At least I can get it away from here.
- 你想怎么做？ - 我不知道 我不知道
- How do you think you're gonna do that? - I don't know. I don't know.
我也许可以智取 或者…
Maybe I can outthink it or…
打野架 记得吗？
The dogfight, remember?
那只是两架战斗机
Those were a couple of jets.
完美的战机
Unbeatable jets.
戒指选中我是有原因的
The ring chose me for a reason.
这就是原因
This is why.
- 听着 也许我… - 不要 不
- Look, I'm probably not… - Please don't. No.
嘿
Hey.
强制疏散
This is a mandatory evacuation.
所有人必须马上撤离街道
Everyone must clear the streets immediately.
Police emergency, everyone must clear the street now.
所有人下车
Everybody off now! Now!
快走 快走！
Go! Go!
快跑
Run!
- 快跑！ - 啊啊！
- Run! - Aah! Aah!
我感觉到你的恐惧在滋生
I feel your fear growing.
你很快就死了
You will be dead soon.
白昼朗朗 黑夜茫茫…
In brightest day, in blackest night…
你死了 我将毁灭你爱过的一切
And when you're gone, I'll destroy everything you ever loved.
鬼魅魍魉 无所遁藏
No evil shall escape my sight.
你的家 你的家人 你们的星球都将消失
Your family, your home, your planet will be no more.
邪科奸党
Let those who worship evil's might…
整个人类的灭绝都是因为你 哈尔·乔丹…
The entire human race will be wiped out because you, Hal Jordan…
惧吾神光
were afraid.
绿灯长明
Beware my power:
万世光芒
Green Lantern's light!
个头越大 死得越快
The bigger you are, the faster you burn.
虽然他戴戒指的时间不长…
Though his time wearing the ring has been brief…
哈尔·乔丹打败了视差怪将永载绿灯军团史册
Hal Jordan's defeat of Parallax will be remembered as long as the Corps exists.
他的事迹提醒我们每个人 戒指选择我们的原因
His actions are a reminder of why the ring chose each of us.
克服恐惧…
To overcome fear…
击败邪恶 使其无所遁藏
and destroy evil wherever it may hide.
绿灯战士们 我们要以我们全部的意志去战斗
As Lanterns, we must fight with all our will.
我们的意志从未如此团结
Our wills haven't always been united.
这次必将团结起来
It's time they were.
- 哈哈哈 - 我是训练他呢 还是训练他呢？
- Ha-ha-ha. - Can I train them or can I train them?
哈尔·乔丹 你鲁莽…
You're impertinent, Hal Jordan.
草率 反复无常 刚愎自用
You're rash, volatile, opinionated.
看来阿宾·苏尔找了一个和他一模一样的
It seems Abin Sur found another just like himself.
哇噢 我永远也习惯不了这个的
Wow, I am never getting used to that.
我的新工作需要到处旅行
My new job requires that I travel.
离开一阵子
Be away for a while.
离开 却不离去
Away, never gone.
哈尔
Hal.
什么？
Yeah?
你能摘下面罩吗？
Can you take off the mask?
太酷了
That's really cool. Ha, ha.
那么 现在该干什么了？
So, what happens now?
我去找点麻烦
I'm gonna go look for trouble.
所有戴过戒指的绿灯战士…
Of all the Lanterns who have ever worn the ring…
有一个的光芒最为耀眼
there was one whose light shined brightest.
起初 他的人性被认为是弱点
At first, his humanity was thought to be a weakness.
但后来却被证明是最伟大的力量
And yet it proved to be his greatest strength.